dwidigitalcameras.com.au 2009-12-28

# Digital World International - Privacy Policy

|  |   
---|---  

|  | 

**

Sign Up to our news Letters and receive Immediate Exculsive Member Benefits!

Including the FREE eBook "Digital Photography - Take pictures like a pro"

** Email Address:  

Search for:  

\- Advance Search

**categories**

**Cameras**   
\- Digital Cameras   
\- Video Cameras   
\- Digital SLR Cameras   
\- Leica Rangefinder Cameras

**Camera Accessories**   
\- Epson Image Viewers   
\- Flashes   
\- Lenses   
\- Memory Cards   
\- Extended Warranties

**Manufactures**   
\- Canon   
\- Casio   
\- Epson   
\- Fuji Film   
\- JVC   
\- Kodak   
\- Leica   
\- MACK CAM   
\- Nikon   
\- Olympus   
\- Panasonic   
\- Pentax   
\- Ricoh   
\- Samsung   
\- SanDisk   
\- Sanyo   
\- Sigma   
\- Sony   
\- Tamron   
\- Tokina   
\- All Manufacturers...

**Information**   
\- Becoming a member   
\- news   
\- testimonials   
\- Top Sellers

**Google Search**

|   
---|---|---  
| 

Home > Frequently Asked Questions > Terms and Conditions > **Privacy Policy**

This is a privacy policy for http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au

**Contact Information**

Our homepage on the Internet is located at http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au

Privacy Policy Supervisor  
Digital World International Limited, PO BOX No. 42  
Fo Tan Post Office  
Hong Kong 

You may contact us by e-mail at sales@dwinternational.net or by phone on (+612) 8005 6499

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Opt-In /Opt-Out**

Registering as a user and opening a user account is optional. To close an account, please email [sales](mailto:sales@dwinternational.net). Your user account will be closed and all information removed from our server within 28 days.

To opt-out of our newsletter subscription, please follow the instructions found at the bottom of the newsletter.

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Dispute Resolution**

If visitors or customers have any issues regarding the privacy practice of our website, please email sales@dwinternational.net or write to our Privacy Policy Supervisor at the address above. Our Privacy Policy Supervisor will respond within 10 working days.

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Data Collection**

When visiting websites, certain information about you and your computer may sometimes be collected. This section explains what information our Privacy Policy Supervisor will collect, and how it is used.

We may collect the following information about our visitors:

username data  
user's home-info data  
dynamic.clickstream data  
dynamic.http data  
dynamic.interactionrecord data  
dynamic.miscdata data  
dynamic.cookies data 

**We collect this information for the following reasons:**

Completion and Support of Current Activity  
Website and System Administration  
Research and Development  
Affirmative Customisation  
One-time Tailoring  
Contacting Visitors for Marketing of Services or products (newsletter subscribers only)  
User Account Registration Data: The user account registration is optional. The data is stored on our server and is used for the sole purpose of speeding up your order process. 

Data collected when customers place an order: We collect customer's Physical Contact Address and Internet Contact Address, as well as credit card information (in the case of credit card payments) for the sole purpose of processing the order and delivering the goods ordered.

newsletter Service: customers may opt-in and opt-out of our newsletter service. Our newsletter subscription service application may collect customer's demographic data in order to provide suitable content to subscribers. customers may opt-out of the newsletter at anytime. Instructions on how to opt-out come with every newsletter sent.

We do NOT sell collected data to 3rd parties: All data collected is used strictly for the purposes defined in the above clauses. We will never sell collected data to any 3rd party individual or organisation.

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Cookies**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not.

Our website uses cookies for the purpose of 'remembering' customers' choice of local site only.  

We carry the latest [Digital Cameras](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/digitalcameras/index.asp "Digital Still Cameras Home Page") (DSC) from [Canon PowerShot and Ixus](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=2 "browse our range of Canon Digital Cameras"), [Nikon Coolpix](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=4 "browse our range of Nikon Digital Cameras"), [Sony CyberShot](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=7 "browse our range of Sony Digital Cameras"), [Pentax Optio](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=6 "browse our range of Pentax Digital Cameras"), [Olympus Stylus, MJU, Tough and FE](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=5 "browse our range of Olympus Digital Cameras"), [Ricoh Caplio and Digital](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=24 "browse our range of Ricoh Digital Cameras"), [Casio Exilim](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=33 "browse our range of Casio Digital Cameras"), [Fuji Film Finepix](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=8 "browse our range of Fuji Film Digital Cameras"), [Samsung i, L and S series](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=56 "browse our range of Samsung Digital Cameras"), [Sanyo Xacti](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=55 "browse our range of Sanyo Digital Cameras"), [Kodak Easyshare](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=9 "browse our range of Kodak Digital Cameras") and [Panasonic Lumix](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=5&brand=10 "browse our range of Panasonic Digital Cameras"). We also have the latest [Digital SLR](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/digitalslrcameras/index.asp "Digital SLR Cameras Home Page") (DSLR) cameras from [Sony Alpha](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=20&brand=7 "browse our range of Sony Alpha Digital SLR Cameras"), [Canon EOS](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=20&brand=2 "browse our range of Canon EOS Digital SLR Cameras"), [Fuji Film S series](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=20&brand=8 "browse our range of Fuji Film Digital SLR Cameras"), [Nikon D series](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=20&brand=4 "browse our range of Nikon Digital SLR Cameras"), [Olympus E series](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=20&brand=5 "browse our range of Olympus Digital SLR Cameras") and [Pentax K series](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=20&brand=6 "browse our range of Pentax Digital SLR Cameras").

Plus we have all your accessories needs including [lenses](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9 "View our range of Lenses") from [Canon EF, EFS and L lenses](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=2 "browse our range of Canon lenses for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras"), [Nikon G, DX, ED and MF Lenses](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=4 "browse our range of Nikon lenses for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras"), [Olympus Standard, Pro and Super Pro](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=5 "Browse or range of Olympus Lenses for Digital SLR Cameras"), [Pentax SMC Lenses](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=6 "browse our range of Pentax lenses for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras"), [Sigma EX, DG and APO Lenses](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=13 "browse our range of Sigma lenses for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras"), [Sony, Carl Zeiss](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=7 "browse our range of Sony Lenses for Sony Digital SLR Cameras") and [Tamron XR, Di and SP Lenses](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=9&brand=14 "browse our range of Tamron lenses for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras") Flashes, flash guns, speedlites and speedlights from [Canon Speedlites](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=10&brand=2 "browse our range of Canon speedlites for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras"), [Nikon Speedlights](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=10&brand=4 "browse our range of Nikon Speedlights for Nikon Digital SLR Cameras "), [Olympus Flash guns](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=10&brand=5 "browse our range of Olympus Flashes for Digital SLR Cameras and Film Cameras") and [Pentax Flashes](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=10&brand=6 "browse our range of Pentax Flashes for Digital SLR Cameras") while we also have a huge range of [Digital video cameras and camcorders](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/digitalvideocameras/index.asp "Digital Video Camera Home Page") including Mini DV, DVD, HDD, Standard Definition (SD) and High Definition (HD) cameras form [Canon DVD, Mini DV and HD](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=8&brand=2 "browse our range of Canon Digital video cameras and camcorders"), [JVC Mini DV, HD and HDD](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=8&brand=11 "browse our range of JVC Digital video cameras and camcorders"), [Panasonic Mini DV, DVD and HDD](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=8&brand=10 "browse our range of Panasonic Digital video cameras and camcorders"), [Samsung HDD](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=8&brand=56 "Browse our range of Samsung Digital Video Cameras and Camcorders") and [Sony Mini DV, DVD, HDD and HD](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/browse.asp?idCategory=8&brand=7 "browse our range of Sony Digital video cameras and camcorders") this makes us your one stop shop for all your digital imaging needs.

Review our bargains and specials which in some cases are better than wholesale. (some people say we are the cheapest or that we have dirt cheap camera prices even cheaper than dirt cheap cameras prices!) So why not review our range of Digital Cameras, Digital SLR Cameras, Digital Video Cameras and Camcorders form manufactures such as Canon, Casio, Fuji (Fuji Film), JVC, Kodak, Nikon, Olympus, Panasonic, Pentax, Ricoh, Samsung, Sanyo and Sony, with this range its never made shopping easier for you to buy at the best and cheapest prices at any online store. So check out deals and grab yourself a bargain. Dont forget when you shop with DWI you get great advice and best of all you save lots of money while getting a Full warranty like you would have if you purchased from any other camera store / shop, so take the worry out of your shopping forget JB Hi-Fi, Harvey Norman, Bing Lee, Dick Smith Electronics (DSE), The Good Guys, Strathfield, Teds, Clive peeters, Clive peters, Retravision, Tandy, Camera store, Digital Rev or even Camera House, we carry a complete range from all manufactures in our digital camera warehouse. Even though we have an extensive range of digital camera, digital SLR (DSLR) cameras and digital video cameras and camcorders we unfortunately do not support the sale or sales of used camera products or equipment.

Digital World International (DWI) delivers its range of Digital Cameras, Digital SLR Cameras and Digital Video Cameras and Camcorders, Lenses, flashes, speedlites, speedlights and other accessories Australia wide to places with in New South Wales (NSW), Queensland (QLD), Victoria (VIC), Tasmania (TAS), Australian Capital territory (ACT), South Australia (SA), Northern territory (NT) and Western Australia (WA) including such places as Adelaide, Albany, Albury, Alice Springs, Armidale, Balladonia, Ballarat, Bellvue Hill, Bendigo, Brisbane, Broadbeach, Broken Hill, Bunbury, Carnarvon, City Beach, Cobar, Broome, Bundaberg, Byron Bay, Cairns, Canberra, Carnarvon, Ceduna, Coffs Harbour, Cooktown, Dampier, Darwin, Derby, Fremantle, Geelong, Geraldton, Georgetown, Gladstone, Glen Innes, Gold Coast, Hobart, Kalgoorlie, Karratha, Karumba, Katherine, Larrimah, Launceston, Lismore, Mackay, Melbourne, Moree, Mount Isa, Moura, Newcastle, Noosa, Perth, Port Hedland, Portland, Port Lincoln, Port Macquarie, Ravensthorpe, Rockhampton, Sunshine Coast, Sydney, Tamworth, Townsville, Tweed Head, Wodonga, Wollongong. Plus anywhere else that FedEx and DHL service in Australia.   
  
---  
  
[ [Privacy Policy](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/help/privacy-policy.asp "Privacy Policy") ]  [ [Terms and Conditions of use and sale](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/help/terms-and-conditions-of-use-and-sale.asp "Terms and Conditions of use and sale") ]  [ [About Us](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/about/index.asp "About Us") ]  [ [Contact Us](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/about/contact.asp "Contact Us") ]  [ [Sitemap](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/store/sitemap.asp "View the sitemap of our web site") ]  [ Click Here to Bookmark Us! ]  [ Top of Page ]  [ [RA Form](http://www.dwidigitalcameras.com.au/help/raform.pdf "Return Autherizeation Form") ]  © 2001 - 2008 Digital World International Limited (DWI). All rights reserved  All brands, logos, images and names are trademarks of their respective companies. Images used are for illustrative purposes only and may not be identical to the product supplied.
